Two brothers out to save everyone else.  But they couldn't save each other.
True Confessions is a crime, drama film directed by Ulu Grosbard.
A cop clashes with his priest brother while investigating
the brutal murder of a young prostitute.
Father Des Spellacy, played by Robert De Niro.
Det. Tom Spellacy, played by Robert Duvall.
Jack Amsterdam, played by Charles Durning.
Frank Crotty, played by Kenneth McMillan.
Dan T. Campion, played by Ed Flanders.
Cardinal Danaher, played by Cyril Cusack.
True Confessions is a 1981 American neo-noir crime drama film directed by Ulu Grosbard and starring Robert De
Niro and Robert Duvall as the brothers Spellacy, a priest and police detective, respectively.
Produced by Chartoff-Winkler Productions, it is adapted from the novel True Confessions by
John Gregory Dunne, loosely based on the 1947 Black Dahlia murder case.
Dunne wrote the screenplay with his wife, novelist Joan Didion.
The film was released on September 25, 1981, receiving
generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
brothel, cop, priest, los angeles, california.
The tone is dark and emotional.